Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Country Files, 1978-1997
  - Singapore Project--Human Rights Mission Report, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 5)
    - Legal Profession Act, 1986 (Box 457, Folder 21)
      - Trade Unions Act, 1967 (Box 457, Folder 41)
        - Academic Freedom (SOM Incident), 1985 (Box 457, Folder 46)
        - Amnesty International (AI), 1987 (Box 457, Folder 47)
        - Annotated Bibliography and Attachments, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 48)
        - Christian Conference of Asia, 1988 (Box 457, Folder 49)
        - Criminal Legal Aid Society, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 50)
        - Foreign Maids, 1984 (Box 457, Folder 51)
        - Labor, 1987-1988 (Box 457, Folder 52)
        - Law Society Reports, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 53)
          (Judiciary/NPPA)
        - Lee, H.G.--Speech--"Managing Transition in Political Leadership", 1987 November 11 (Box 457, Folder 54)
        - Minutes of Communications and Information Materials--rec'd from permanent secretary, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 1)
        - Seow, Frances--Independence of Judiciary and Human Rights, undated (Box 458, Folder 2)
        - Singapore
        - General, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 3)
        - Opposition, 1986 (Box 458, Folder 4)
        - Politics--People's Action Party (PAP), 1986-1987 (Box 458, Folder 5)
        - Press, 1987-1988 (Box 458, Folder 6)
        - Foreign Correspondents Association, 1986-1987 (Box 458, Folder 7)
        - United States
        - Relations, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 8)
        - State Department Human Rights Report, undated (Box 458, Folder 9)
        - Subhas Anandan
        - Disciplinary Proceeding, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 10)
        - "Use of Emergency Regulations in Peacetime in the Region", undated (Box 458, Folder 11)
        - Team MP, 1987-1988 (Box 458, Folder 12)
        - Torture, 1983 (Box 458, Folder 13)
        - Internal Security Act
        - Advisory Board Representations--Tang Fong Har and Ching Suan Tze, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 14)
        - Cases, 1971-1978 (Box 458, Folder 15)
        - Catholic Church Materials--DeSouza/Yong Correspondence, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 16)
        - Cheng, Vincent--Letters, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 17)
        - Chew, K.C.--Notes, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 18)
        - Chia Thye Poh--Case, 1989-1991 (Box 458, Folder 19)
        - DeSouza, Kevin--Advisory Board--References, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 20)
        - Detention, 1980 1987 (Box 458, Folder 21)
        - Emergency Committee for Human Rights (HR) in Singapore, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 22)
        - Ex-Detainee's Statement--Tsuan Tze, undated (Box 458, Folder 23)
        - Internal Security Act (ISA) (Box 458, Folder 23)
        - Arrests/Embassy Mats., 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 458, Folder 24-25)
        - Confidential, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 26)
          [restricted until 2063]
        - International Mission of Jurists to Singapore Report, 1987 July (Box 458, Folder 27)
        - May and June Detentions, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 28)
        - Parliament (Written Questions) Detentions, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 29)
        - Past Detentions (General), 1980-1981 1987 (Box 458, Folder 30)
        - Report of the Commission of Inquiry on Investigations Concerning the Late Mr. The Cheang Wan, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 31)
        - Restriction Orders, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 32)
        - Pro Bono
        - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 458, Folder 33-34)
        - Memoranda, 1989 (Box 458, Folder 35)
        - Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1989 (Box 458, Folder 36)
        - Newsletters--Asia Watch (AW), 1988 (Box 458, Folder 37)
        - Parliamentary Date re, Bills Related to Judiciary, 1986 (Box 458, Folder 38)
        - Recent Materials, 1988 (Box 458, Folder 39)
        - Telephone List, undated (Box 458, Folder 40)
        - Tan Wah Piow, Let the People Judge: confessions of the most wanted person in Singapore, 1987 (Box 458, Folder 40)
        - Teo Soh Lung--Case, 1989, (6 folders) (Box 459, Folder 1-6)
        - To file--Singapore, 1989-1990 (Box 459, Folder 7)
        - Torture, 1989 (Box 459, Folder 8)
        - Trade and Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 459, Folder 9)
        - United States
        - Congressional Advocacy, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 10-11)
        - Congressional Hearings, 1988-1990 (Box 459, Folder 12)
        - Congressional Testimony, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 13-14)
        - Unidentified Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 459, Folder 15)
        - Vincent Cheng and Teo Soh Lung, 1989 (Box 459, Folder 16)
        - South Korea
        - Asia Watch (AW)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 17-18)
        - Work, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 459, Folder 19-21)
      - Communication w/Government, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 22-23)
      - Contacts, 1989-1990 (Box 459, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence--General, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 25-26)
      - Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 459, Folder 27)
      - Foreign Relations, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 28-29)
      - General Background, 1989-1993, (5 folders) (Box 459, Folder 30-34)
      - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 459, Folder 35-36)
      - International Human Rights Organizations, 1989-1990 (Box 459, Folder 37)
      - Killings, 1989 (Box 459, Folder 38)
      - Korea Church Coalition--Korea Update, 1989-1991 (Box 459, Folder 39)
      - Korea Church Coalition, 1993 (Box 460, Folder 1)
      - Korea Report, 1989 (Box 460, Folder 2)
      - Korea Society News, 1992-1993 (Box 460, Folder 3)
      - Kwanghu, 1989 (Box 460, Folder 4)
      - Legal System/Texts, 1988-1989 (Box 460, Folder 5)
      - Military and Government, 1988-1990 (Box 460, Folder 6)
      - Missions/Visits, 1989-1990 (Box 460, Folder 7)
      - North/South Relations, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 460, Folder 8-9)
      - Past Abuses, 1988-1990 (Box 460, Folder 10)
      - Political Opposition, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 460, Folder 11-12)
      - Press, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 460, Folder 13-14)
      - Prisons/Prisoners, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 460, Folder 15-16)
      - Shim Jae-Kyun--Legal Complaint with documentation (Korean), 1997 April (Box 460, Folder 17)
      - Torture, 1988-1989 1991 (Box 460, Folder 18)
      - Trade and Aid, 1988-1991 (Box 460, Folder 19)
      - Trade Unions/Labor Rights, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 460, Folder 20-21)
      - United States--Congressional Advocacy, 1989-1991 (Box 460, Folder 22)
      - U.S. Korea Review, 1994-1995 (Box 460, Folder 23)
    - Sri Lanka
    - Ariyaratne, A.T., "Peace Making in Sri Lanka in the Buddhist Context", 1987 (Box 460, Folder 24)
    - Asia Watch (AW)
    - News from Asia Watch, 1989-1991 (Box 460, Folder 25)
    - Work, 1988-1990 (Box 460, Folder 26)
    - Campaign for Democracy and Human Rights in Sri Lanka
    - "Not Mere Imperfection: 12 Years of UNP Misrule", undated (Box 460, Folder 27)
    - Sri Lanka Newsletter, 1990-1992 (Box 460, Folder 28)
    - Civil Rights Movement of Sri Lanka, 1990-1993 1995 (Box 460, Folder 29)
    - Communication w/Government, 1994 (Box 460, Folder 30)
    - DANA: The International Journal of the Sarvodaya Movement, 1991 (Box 460, Folder 31)
    - Dentist Case, 1991 (Box 460, Folder 32)
    - Eelam Update, 1992-1993 1995-1996 (Box 460, Folder 33)
    - Embassy of Sri Lanka
    - Sri Lanka News, 1995-1997 (Box 460, Folder 34)
    - Sri Lanka News Bulletin, 1990, (5 folders) (Box 460, Folder 35-39)
    - Sri Lanka Newsletter, 1993-1995 (Box 460, Folder 40)
    - Sri Lanka Update, 1993-1995 (Box 460, Folder 41)
  - General, 1989-1996, (29 folders) (Box 461, Folder 1-29)
  - General, 1995-1996, (7 folders) (Box 462, Folder 1-7)
  - Government Documents and Press Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 462, Folder 8)
  - Guthrie, Jeanine--Correspondence, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 462, Folder 9-10)
  - Inform: Sri Lanka Information Monitor, 1991-1996, (4 folders) (Box 462, Folder 11-14)
  - International Alert, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 15)
  - Les Droits Tamouls, 1994-1996 (Box 462, Folder 16)
  - Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam
  - Peace Initiative, 1991 (Box 462, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 462, Folder 18)
  - Monitors, 1990 (Box 462, Folder 19)
  - Nadesan Centre, 1996 (Box 462, Folder 20)
  - Network, 1994 (Box 462, Folder 21)
  - News Clips, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 462, Folder 22-24)
  - News Clips, 1990-1993, (18 folders) (Box 463, Folder 1-18)
  - News Clips, 1994-1996, (10 folders) (Box 464, Folder 1-10)
  - Pravāda, 1991 (Box 464, Folder 11)
  - Press, 1987-1996, (10 folders) (Box 464, Folder 12-21)
  - Publications--Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 464, Folder 22)
  - Sarvodaya Strategic Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 464, Folder 23)
  - Selvanithi, Thiyagarajah (poet), 1992 (Box 464, Folder 24)
  - Sri Lanka Monitor, 1993-1996 (Box 464, Folder 25)
  - Social Justice, 1990-1991 (Box 464, Folder 26)
  - Tamil Information: News Bulletin of the Tamil Information Centre, 1991-1996 (Box 464, Folder 27)
  - Tamil Land, 1993-1994 (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Tamil Voice: Newsletter of the Ilankai Thamil Sangam, 1995-1996 (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 465, Folder 3-4)
  - Government Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 465, Folder 5)
  - University Teachers for Human Rights (JAFFNA), 1991 (Box 465, Folder 6)
  - Wires, 1994-1995, (4 folders) (Box 465, Folder 7-10)
  - Taiwan
  - Asia Watch (AW)--Correspondence, 1989 1991 (Box 465, Folder 11)
  - Contacts, 1989-1990 (Box 465, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence--General, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Relations, 1989-1992 (Box 465, Folder 15)
  - General Background, 1989-1992 1994, (2 folders) (Box 465, Folder 16-17)
  - Human Rights Violations, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 18)
  - International Human Rights Organizations, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 19)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1989-1992 (Box 465, Folder 20)
  - Military and Government, 1989-1992 (Box 465, Folder 21)
  - Missions/Visits, 1989 (Box 465, Folder 22)
  - Political Opposition, 1989-1992 (Box 465, Folder 23)
  - Press, 1989 (Box 465, Folder 24)
  - Prisons/Prisoners, 1988-1991 (Box 465, Folder 25)
  - Spies, 1990-1991 (Box 465, Folder 26)
  - Taiwan Communiqué: International Committee for Human Rights in Taiwan, 1995 (Box 465, Folder 27)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1988-1989 (Box 465, Folder 28)
  - Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 29)
  - AIDS/HIV
  - Human Rights (HR) Instruments/Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 465, Folder 30)
  - Thailand--General, 1993-1994 (Box 465, Folder 31)
  - Bangkok Massacre, 1992 May
  - Amnesty/Missing, 1992 (Box 465, Folder 32)
  - "‘Bloody May ': Excessive Use of Lethal Force in Bangkok the Events of May 17-20, 1992", 1992 October 1992 (Box 465, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Popular Democracy, 1992-1993 (Box 465, Folder 34)
  - General, 1992-1993 (Box 465, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Congressional Reaction, 1991-1992 (Box 465, Folder 36)
  - Burma Policy, 1994-1995 (Box 465, Folder 37)
  - Burmese Refugees
  - In Thailand, 1990-1993 (Box 465, Folder 38)
  - Repatriation by Thailand, 1989-1991 (Box 465, Folder 39)
  - Communication w/Government, 1990-1993 (Box 465, Folder 40)
  - Contacts, 1991-1992 (Box 465, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence--General, 1990-1992 (Box 465, Folder 42)
  - Coup, 1991 (Box 465, Folder 43)
  - Demonstrations, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 466, Folder 1-2)
  - Drugs, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 3)
  - Environment, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Relations
  - Australia, 1994 (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - Cambodia, 1994-1995 (Box 466, Folder 6)
  - China, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 7)
  - Indonesia, 1994 (Box 466, Folder 8)
  - Japan, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 9)
  - Laos, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 10)
  - Malaysia, undated (Box 466, Folder 11)
  - Vietnam, 1993-1994 (Box 466, Folder 12)
  - General, 1989-1995, (9 folders) (Box 466, Folder 13-21)
  - Hmong-Lao Human Rights Council, 1993 (Box 466, Folder 22)
  - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1992 (Box 466, Folder 23)
  - Immigration Detention Centre (IDC), 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 466, Folder 24-25)
  - International Human Rights Organizations, 1990-1993 (Box 466, Folder 26)
  - Killings, 1990-1992 (Box 466, Folder 27)
  - Lintner, Bertil (Swedish journalist), 1990-1991 (Box 467, Folder 1)
  - Media, 1992 (Box 467, Folder 2)
  - Neutral Camp, 1990 1993 (Box 467, Folder 3)
  - NGO Publications, 1991-1993 (Box 467, Folder 4)
  - Opposition Abuses, 1992 (Box 467, Folder 5)
  - Police, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 6)
  - Prisons, 1994 (Box 467, Folder 7)
  - Sea Gypsies, 1993 (Box 467, Folder 8)
  - Sex Trade--News Clips, 1992-1993 (Box 467, Folder 9-10)
  - Sex Workers
  - Arrests on sex-abuse, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 11)
  - Child Abuse, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers in United States, 1991-1993 (Box 467, Folder 13)
  - Prostitution in Thailand, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 14)
  - Raids, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 15)
  - Sex tourism, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 16)
  - Thai-government on Prostitution, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 17)
  - Thai women in Japan, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 18)
  - South--Muslims, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 19)
  - Trade and Aid, 1988-1992 (Box 467, Folder 20)
  - Trip Notes, 1993 August (Box 467, Folder 21)
  - Wildlife Fund, 1992-1994 (Box 467, Folder 22)
  - Women
  - AIDS, child prostitution, 1991-1993 (Box 467, Folder 23)
  - Friends of Women Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 467, Folder 24)
  - Trafficking in Women, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 25)
  - Voices of Thai Women, 1989-1992 (Box 467, Folder 26)
  - Women's Education for Advancement and Empowerment (WEAVE), 1993 (Box 467, Folder 26)
  - Workers' Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 467, Folder 27)
  - World Bank, 1990-1996, (4 folders) (Box 467, Folder 28-31)
  - Vanuatu--General, 1989-1990 (Box 467, Folder 32)
  - Vietnam
  - Amerasians in Vietnam, 1988 (Box 467, Folder 33)
  - Amnesty International (AI)--Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 467, Folder 34)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 467, Folder 35)
  - News, 1988-1992 (Box 467, Folder 36)
  - Asylum Seekers (Box 468)
  - China and Hong Kong, 1980 1983-1987 1991 (Box 468, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong Government--Advocacy, 1992 (Box 468, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights League, 1990-1991 (Box 468, Folder 3)
  - UN High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR)--Advocacy, 1992-1994 (Box 468, Folder 4)
  - Vietnamese Refugee: Interviews with Asylum-Seekers, undated (Box 468, Folder 5)
  - Bangkok Trip, 1991 June 12-19 (Box 468, Folder 6)
  - Boat People, 1989-1993, (3 folders) (Box 468, Folder 7-9)
  - The Bridge--Indochina Resource Action Center (IRAC), 1990-1996 (Box 468, Folder 10)
  - Buddhists
  - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 468, Folder 11)
  - General, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 468, Folder 12-13)
  - United Buddhist Church, 1992-1994 (Box 468, Folder 14)
  - Contacts, 1991 (Box 468, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence--General, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 468, Folder 16-17)
  - Denney, Stephen--Articles, 1990 (Box 468, Folder 18)
  - Dinah PoKempner--Vietnam materials, 1991 (Box 468, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Europe--Vietnamese Contract Labor, 1990-1991 (Box 468, Folder 20)
  - Foreigners, 1990-1991 (Box 468, Folder 21)
  - Free Speech, Association, 1990-1995 (Box 468, Folder 22)
  - General, 1985-1991, (5 folders) (Box 468, Folder 23-27)
  - General, 1990-1993, (15 folders) (Box 469, Folder 1-15)
  - Government on Human Rights, 1993-1995 (Box 469, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Abuses, 1988-1991 (Box 469, Folder 17)
  - Human Rights League, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 469, Folder 18-20)
  - Human Rights--Statements, undated (Box 469, Folder 21)
  - Law--Press Clips, 1991-1995 (Box 469, Folder 22)
  - Legal System, 1976-1991 (Box 469, Folder 23)
  - "Miss Saigon's Children: The United States' Continuing International Obligation to Amerasians", 1992 (Box 469, Folder 24)
  - Missions/Visits, 1990-1993, (3 folders) (Box 469, Folder 25-27)
  - Montagnards, 1990-1991 (Box 469, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1990-1992 (Box 469, Folder 29)
  - Nung Refugees in Hong Kong and Deportation to Vietnam (Box 470)
  - Advocacy, 1992 (Box 470, Folder 1)
  - Background Research, 1991-1994 (Box 470, Folder 2)
  - Casework--Lau Cong Tac and Lau Cong Huan, 1993 (Box 470, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 470, Folder 4)
  - Lists, petitions, 1990-1992 (Box 470, Folder 5)
  - Nhi, Vong A.--Repatriation Case, 1992 (Box 470, Folder 6)
  - Politics, 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 7)
  - Press and Congress, 1994 (Box 470, Folder 8)
  - Refugees
  - Casework Lists, 1993 (Box 470, Folder 9)
  - Dang Hoang Ha--Casework, 1993-1994 (Box 470, Folder 10)
  - Liang Kieu--Casework, 1991-1992 (Box 470, Folder 11)
  - Refugee Status Review Board (RSRB)--Cases and Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 470, Folder 12)
  - Refugees in Malaysia--Letter from Doan Minh Son--Kerayong Camp, undated (Box 470, Folder 13)
  - Religion, 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 14)
  - Repression and Dissent, 1991 (Box 470, Folder 15)
  - Shapiro, Judy--Detention, 1993 (Box 470, Folder 16)
  - Speech/Press, 1990-1992 (Box 470, Folder 17)
  - Trade/Economy, 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 18)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 19)
  - Hearings, 1992-1993 (Box 470, Folder 20)
  - Policy, 1990-1991 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box 470, Folder 21-23)
  - Vietnam Democracy, 1994-1997 (Box 470, Folder 24)
  - Vietnam Insight, 1991-1994 (Box 470, Folder 25)
  - Vong Y. Phy--Refugee Status, 1992-1994 (Box 470, Folder 26)
  - Wires, 1991 January -July (6 folders) (Box 470, Folder 27-32)
  - Writers, 1991-1994 (Box 470, Folder 33)
- Series 3: General Files, 1988-1997
  General files are arranged alphabetically by subject. Subject files consist of newsletters, press releases, reports and project materials dealing with women's issues and the World Bank.
  - Asia Watch (AW)
    - Chron. Files--India, 1992 1994-1995, (5 folders) (Box 471, Folder 1-5)
    - General Files (Box 472)
    - Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Advocacy Work--Job Description, 1995 January 30 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Mission, 1991 May (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Board/Committee Meetings, 1990-1993, (6 folders) (Box 472, Folder 4-9)
    - Budget, 1988-1994, (5 folders) (Box 472, Folder 10-14)
    - Correspondence--General, 1991-1993 (Box 472, Folder 15)
    - Fund for Free Expression, 1992 (Box 472, Folder 16)
    - Human Rights Watch
    - General, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 472, Folder 17-18)
    - Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 472, Folder 19)
  - Interns, 1990-1992 (Box 472, Folder 20)
  - Jones, Sidney (Box 473)
  - "Asians Deserve Their Rights, Like Everyone Else", International Herald Tribune, 1993 April 21 (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - Chron. Files, 1989-1886, (14 folders) (Box 473, Folder 2-15)
  - News from Asia Watch, 1989-1997, (15 folders) (Box 474, Folder 1-15)
  - Personnel Info., 1994 (Box 474, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, Faxes and Statements
  - Faxes from Geneva, 1997 April (Box 474, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, Statements, Testimony, 1994-1996 (Box 474, Folder 18)
  - Sanctions Policy, 1993 (Box 474, Folder 19)
  - Training, 1992-1994, (2 folders) (Box 474, Folder 20-21)
  - Press, 1990-1992, (5 folders) (Box 475, Folder 1-5)
  - General
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU)--Cases, 1996 (Box 475, Folder 6)
  - Asia Pacific Forum on Women, Law and Development, 1988 (Box 475, Folder 7)
  - Asia-Pacific Peoples' Forum on Peace and Development, 1991 (Box 475, Folder 8)
  - Asia Society--"The Future of U.S.-Indochina Relations", 1989 September (Box 475, Folder 9)
  - Asian Concept of Human Rights, 1991-1994 (Box 475, Folder 10)
  - Asian Human Rights Commission Newsletter, 1992 July (Box 475, Folder 11)
  - Asian Students Association (ASA)--ASA News, 1992 (Box 475, Folder 12)
  - Child Labor, 1994 (Box 475, Folder 13)
  - Disappearances, 1991 (Box 475, Folder 14)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1991 (Box 475, Folder 15)
  - Human Rights Brief, 1995 (Box 475, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Defender, 1992-1994 (Box 475, Folder 17)
  - Human Rights Issues--Congressional Advocacy, 1989-1992 (Box 475, Folder 18)
  - Human Rights Monitor, 1989-1997, (5 folders) (Box 475, Folder 19-23)
  - Human Rights Organizations
  - Newsletters, 1989-1993, (3 folders) (Box 475, Folder 24-26)
  - Other, 1988-1991, (3 folders) (Box 476, Folder 1-3)
  - Immigration, 1989-1992 (Box 476, Folder 4)
  - Informal Sector Service Center (INSEC) Bulletin, 1991 (Box 476, Folder 5)
  - International Labor Office (ILO)
  - International Labor Conference, 1989 (Box 476, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 476, Folder 7)
  - World of Work: The Magazine of the ILO, 1993-1994 (Box 476, Folder 8)
  - International Movement Against All Forms of Discrimination and Racism (IMADR) Review, 1993-1994 (Box 476, Folder 9)
  - International Work Group for Indigenous Affairs (IWGIA) (Box 476, Folder 9)
  - Indigenous Affairs, 1995 (Box 476, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 476, Folder 11)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Union--95th Conference, 1996 April (Box 476, Folder 12)
  - Landmines, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 476, Folder 13-14)
  - Miscellaneous--Various Countries, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 476, Folder 15-16)
  - NGO Statements (Asian Concept), 1992-1994 (Box 476, Folder 17)
  - OMCT/SOS Torture, 1992-1996 (Box 476, Folder 18)
  - Refugees, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 476, Folder 19-20)
  - Rumbrar, Jan B., 1995 (Box 476, Folder 21)
  - Speahrhead: Bulletin of the Society for the Protection of East Asians' Human Rights, 1979-1983 (Box 476, Folder 22)
  - Torture: Quarterly Journal on Rehabilitation of Torture Victims and Prevention of Torture, 1995-1996 (Box 476, Folder 22)
  - United Nations--"Chinese Diplomacy, Western Hypocrisy and the UN Human Rights Commission" (HRW Report), 1997 March (Box 477)
  - Africa, 1995-1997 (Box 477, Folder 1)
  - Asia, 1995-1997 (Box 477, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 477, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Europe, 1995-1996 (Box 477, Folder 4)
  - Latin America, 1995-1997 (Box 477, Folder 5)
  - Lists, Notes, UN Commission Drafts, 1995-1997 (Box 477, Folder 6)
  - Relations of UNHRC Members--Not China, 1995-1997 (Box 477, Folder 7)
  - United States, 1996-1997 (Box 477, Folder 8)
  - Western Europe, 1996-1997 (Box 477, Folder 9)
  - 4th World Conference on Women (1995)--Publications, 1994-1995, (11 folders) (Box 477, Folder 10-20)
  - UN Watch, 1989 (Box 477, Folder 21)
  - World Conference on Human Rights (Vienna, Austria), 1993 June (3 folders) (Box 478, Folder 1-3)
  - World Summit for Social Development, 1994-1996, (10 folders) (Box 478, Folder 4-13)
  - Women's Issues, 1988-1990 (Box 478, Folder 14)
  - Women's Project, 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box 478, Folder 15-16)
  - World Bank--"Forcible Resettlement in World Bank Projects", 1994 January (Box 478, Folder 17)
- Series 4: Jeannine Guthrie, Sri Lanka Files1985-1997
  This series consists of subject files associated with Jeannine Guthrie's work as a research associate for Sri Lankan issues and later as NGO Liaison. The files are arranged alphabetically and comprise such issues as military operations, refugees, and women's rights.
  - Amnesty International (AI), 1993 (Box 479, Folder 1)
  - Appendices--Accountability, 1990-1991 (Box 479, Folder 2)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Sri Lanka, 1990 1992-1993 1995 (Box 479, Folder 3)
  - Work, 1992-1995 (Box 479, Folder 4)
  - Asylum, 1991-1994 (Box 479, Folder 5)
  - Children, 1992 (Box 479, Folder 6)
  - Chron. Files, 1992-1995, (18 folders) (Box 479, Folder 7-24)
  - Chronology of Events, 1988 February-1992 August (Box 480, Folder 1)
  - Communications w/Government, 1995 (Box 480, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence--Miscellaneous, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 480, Folder 3-4)
  - Disappearances, 1992 (Box 480, Folder 5)
  - Donors Meeting, 1993 (Box 480, Folder 6)